{"data":[{"question":"In the spirit of the naturalist writers, that author's work portrays man's struggle for surviving.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"were","c":"received with mixed emotions","d":"of both governments","answer":"2","explain":" - Were-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Stephen Crane's story is a clinical portrayal of man as an animal trapped by the fear and hunger.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were","b":"that which","c":"helped her","d":"the other","answer":"2","explain":" - That which-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Engineers succeeded on putting more and more components on each silicon chip.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Joel","b":"smoking has","c":"caused him to gain","d":"become irritable","answer":"1","explain":" - Joe-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"For a long time, this officials have been known throughout the country as political bosses and law enforcers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"what did happen","b":"last night","c":"unable to","d":"tell them","answer":"1","explain":" - Did happen-> happened","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Nora hardly never misses an opportunity to play in the tennis tournaments.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"test","b":"we","c":"not to open","d":"told us to do so","answer":"2","explain":" - We-> us","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Because of the severe snow storm and the road blocks, the air force dropped food and medical supplies close the city.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Our new","b":"had been living","c":"since","d":"before moving to","answer":"3","explain":" - Since-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Hummingbirds are the only birds capable to fly backward as well as forward, up, and down.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would of","b":"of the planning","c":"had to deliver","d":"at a convention","answer":"1","explain":" - Would of-> would","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The news of the president's treaty negotiations with the foreign government were received with mixed emotions by the citizens of both governments.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"suppose","b":"all of chapter","c":"answer","d":"for tomorrow's class","answer":"1","explain":" - Suppose-> supposed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Angie's bilingual ability and previous experience were the qualities that which helped her get the job over all the other candidates.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"our","b":"gave us","c":"than","d":"yours gave you","answer":"3","explain":" - Than-> from","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Joel giving up smoking has caused him to gain weight and become irritable with his acquaintances.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In the sixteenth","b":"became involved in foreign","c":"several other","d":"of finance","answer":"4","explain":" - Of finance-> to finance","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}